Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3, Section 1: Boxes 1-22
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3, Section 1: Boxes 1-22
- Box: 4, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Alcoholism Program, Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Box: 4, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Orientation Program for Newly Hired Non-Exempt Salaried Employees, 1966; Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Box: 4, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Bethlehem Pension Benefits for Eligible Steel Hourly Paid Employees, 1975; Publication (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Box: 4, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Pension Benefits for Eligible Bethlehem Salaried Employees, 1975; Publication (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Box: 4, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Program of Insurance Benefits for Eligible Hourly Paid Employees, 1972; Publication (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Box: 4, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Program of Insurance Benefits for Exempt Salaried Employees, 1975; Publication (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Box: 4, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Program of Insurance Benefits for Non-Exempt Salaried Employees, 1972; Publication (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Box: 4, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: The Proposed Bethlehem-Youngstown Merger, 1955; Publication (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Box: 4, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: The Truth About the Local Working Conditions Issue, Publication (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Box: 4, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: The Truth About Seniority and 'Union-Busting', 1959; Publication (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Box: 4, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Bethlehem's Offer to the Union: Facts for Employees, 1960; Publication (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Box: 4, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Questions and Answers on Local Working Conditions, 1959; Publication (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Box: 4, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Program of Long Term Disability Insurance for Exempt Salaried Employees, 1967; Publication (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Box: 4, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: A Summary of Benefits for Exempt Salaried Employees in the Steel Division, 1970; Publication (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Box: 4, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Your Benefits as a Non-Exempt Salaried Employee in the Steel Division, 1969; Publication (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Box: 4, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Supplemental Unemployment Benefits, Publication (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Box: 4, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Pension Plan of Bethlehem Steel Corporation (Delaware), 1957; Publication (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Box: 4, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: This Is Bethlehem Steel, 1959; Publication (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Box: 4, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Life Insurance Sickness and Accident Insurance Hospitalization and Surgical Benefits for Hourly Paid Employees of Bethlehem Steel Corporation, 1954; Publication (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Box: 4, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Safety Bulletin Vol.33, No.2, 1968; Publication (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Item 2: Safety Bulletin Vol.33, No.3, 1968; Publication (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Item 3: Safety Bulletin Vol.33, No.4, 1968; Publication (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Item 4: Safety Bulletin Vol.33, No.5, 1968; Publication (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Item 5: Safety Bulletin Vol.33, No.6, 1968; Publication (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Item 6: Safety Bulletin Vol.33, No.7, 1968; Publication (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Item 7: Safety Bulletin Vol.33, No.8, 1968; Publication (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Item 8: Safety Bulletin Vol.33, No.9, 1968; Publication (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Item 9: Safety Bulletin Vol.33, No.10, 1968; Publication (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Item 10: Safety Bulletin Vol.33, No.11, 1968; Publication (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Item 11: Safety Bulletin Vol.34, No.1, 1969; Publication (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Item 12: Safety Bulletin Vol.34, No.2, 1969; Publication (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Item 13: Safety Bulletin Vol.34, No.3, 1969; Publication (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Item 14: Safety Bulletin Vol.34, No.4, 1969; Publication (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Item 15: Safety Bulletin Vol.34, No.5, 1969; Publication (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Item 16: Safety Bulletin Vol.34, No.6, 1969; Publication (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Item 17: Safety Bulletin Vol.34, No.7, 1969; Publication (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Item 18: Safety Bulletin Vol.34, No.8, 1969; Publication (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Item 19: Safety Bulletin Vol.34, No.9, 1969; Publication (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Item 20: Safety Bulletin Vol.34, No.10, 1969; Publication (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Item 21: Safety Bulletin Vol.34, No.11, 1969; Publication (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Item 22: Safety Bulletin Vol.34, No.12, 1969; Publication (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Item 23: Safety Bulletin Vol.32, No.5, 1967; Publication (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Item 24: Safety Bulletin Vol.32, No.6, 1967; Publication (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Item 25: Safety Bulletin Vol.32, No.7, 1967; Publication (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Item 26: Safety Bulletin Vol.32, No.8, 1967; Publication (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Item 27: Safety Bulletin Vol.32, No.9, 1967; Publication (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Item 28: Safety Bulletin Vol.32, No.10, 1967; Publication (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Item 29: Safety Bulletin Vol.32, No.11, 1967; Publication (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Item 30: Safety Bulletin Vol.31, No.1 - Vol.32, No.4, 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Item 31: Safety Bulletin Vol.32, No.12, 1967; Publication (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Item 32: Safety Bulletin Vol.33, No.1, 1968; Publication (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Box: 4, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Safety Bulletin Vol.29, No.1, 1964; Publication (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Item 2: Safety Bulletin Vol.29, No.2, 1964; Publication (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Item 3: Safety Bulletin Vol.29, No.3, 1964; Publication (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Item 4: Safety Bulletin Vol.29, No.4, 1964; Publication (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Item 5: Safety Bulletin Vol.29, No.5, 1964; Publication (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Item 6: Safety Bulletin Vol.29, No.6, 1964; Publication (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Item 7: Safety Bulletin Vol.29, No.7, 1964; Publication (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Item 8: Safety Bulletin Vol.29, No.8, 1964; Publication (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Item 9: Safety Bulletin Vol.29, No.9, 1964; Publication (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Item 10: Safety Bulletin Vol.29, No.10, 1964; Publication (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Item 11: Safety Bulletin Vol.29, No.11, 1964; Publication (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Item 12: Safety Bulletin Vol.29, No.12, 1964; Publication (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Item 13: Safety Bulletin Vol.30, No.1, 1965; Publication (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Item 14: Safety Bulletin Vol.30, No.2, 1965; Publication (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Item 15: Safety Bulletin Vol.30, No.3, 1965; Publication (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Item 16: Safety Bulletin Vol.30, No.4, 1965; Publication (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Item 17: Safety Bulletin Vol.30, No.5, 1965; Publication (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Item 18: Safety Bulletin Vol.30, No.6, 1965; Publication (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Item 19: Safety Bulletin Vol.30, No.7, 1965; Publication (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Item 20: Safety Bulletin Vol.30, No.8, 1965; Publication (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Item 21: Safety Bulletin Vol.30, No.9, 1965; Publication (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Item 22: Safety Bulletin Vol.30, No.10, 1965; Publication (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Item 23: Safety Bulletin Vol.30, No.11, 1965; Publication (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Item 24: Safety Bulletin Vol.30, No.12, 1965; Publication (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Item 25: Safety Bulletin Vol.35, No.1, 1970; Publication (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Item 26: Safety Bulletin Vol.35, No.2, 1970; Publication (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Item 27: Safety Bulletin Vol.35, No.3, 1970; Publication (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Item 28: Safety Bulletin Vol.28, No.1 - Vol.28, No.12, 1963; Publication (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Item 29: Safety Bulletin Vol.27, No.1 - Vol.27, No.12, 1962; Publication (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Box: 4, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Your Boeing Retirement Plan, Publication (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Box: 4, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Supervision's Responsibilities in the Safety Program, Publication (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Box: 4, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Between the Lines at Boeing, Publication (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Box: 4, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Boeing Graduate Study Program, Publication (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Box: 4, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Reinstatement Rights of Persons Who Leave Positions to Enter Military Service, Publication (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Box: 4, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Group Coverage for Boeing Employees, 1959; Publication (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Box: 4, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Performance Analysis, 1950; Publication (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Box: 4, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: The New Health Protection Plan for Boeing Employees, 1952; Publication (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Box: 4, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Invention Incentive Plan, Publication (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Box: 4, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: The Best in Medical Science for You: King County Medical Service, Publication (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Box: 4, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Boeing Sickness and Accident Benefits, 1952; Publication (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Box: 4, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Protect Yourself and Your Family, Publication (Box 4, Folder 38)
- Box: 4, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Comprehensive Medical Insurance Plan for Salaried Employees, 1960; Publication (Box 4, Folder 39)
- Box: 4, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Training Opportunities for Boeing Employees Voluntary Training Program, Publication (Box 4, Folder 40)
- Box: 4, Folder: 41, Publication (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Employee Plan of Major Medical, Surgical, Hospital Reimbursement Insurance, 1959; Publication (Box 4, Folder 41)
- Box: 4, Folder: 42, Publication (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: Ideas Pay Off, Publication (Box 4, Folder 42)
- Box: 4, Folder: 43, Publication (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: Health Protection Plan for Boeing Employees, Publication (Box 4, Folder 43)
- Box: 4, Folder: 44, Publication (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: For Your Information, Publication (Box 4, Folder 44)
- Box: 4, Folder: 45, Publication (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Item 1: Hourly Employees Group Insurance Plan, 1958; Publication (Box 4, Folder 45)
- Box: 4, Folder: 46, Publication (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Item 1: Your Group Insurance Program, 1963; Publication (Box 4, Folder 46)
- Box: 4, Folder: 47, Publication (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Item 1: Boeing Salaried Employees Group Life Insurance Plan, 1959; Publication (Box 4, Folder 47)
- Box: 4, Folder: 48, Publication (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Item 1: Sickness and Accident Benefits: Who Can Participate, Publication (Box 4, Folder 48)
- Box: 4, Folder: 49, Publication (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Item 1: You Choose the Doctor, Publication (Box 4, Folder 49)
- Box: 4, Folder: 50, Publication (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Item 1: Boeing Employees' Group Life Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 4, Folder 50)
- Box: 4, Folder: 51, Publication (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Item 1: The Boeing Hourly Insurance Program, 1966; Publication (Box 4, Folder 51)
- Box: 4, Folder: 52, Publication (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Item 1: Continuing Engineering Studies (1968-69), 1969; Publication (Box 4, Folder 52)
- Box: 4, Folder: 53, Publication (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Item 1: Employee Insurance Program for Salaried Personnel, 1968; Publication (Box 4, Folder 53)
- Box: 4, Folder: 54, Publication (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Item 1: Employee Insurance Program for Hourly Personnel, 1968; Publication (Box 4, Folder 54)
- Box: 4, Folder: 55, Publication (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Item 1: The Boeing Company-Huntsville, Alabama, Publication (Box 4, Folder 55)
- Box: 4, Folder: 56, Publication (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Item 1: Hourly Payroll Authorization, Publication (Box 4, Folder 56)
- Box: 4, Folder: 57, Publication (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Item 1: Boeing Factory Direct and Indirect Job Evaluation Plan, Publication (Box 4, Folder 57)
- Box: 4, Folder: 58, Publication (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Item 1: Ideas are Ammunition, 1941; Publication (Box 4, Folder 58)
- Box: 4, Folder: 59, Publication (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Item 1: Talent Scouting, 1946; Publication (Box 4, Folder 59)
- Box: 4, Folder: 60, Publication (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Item 1: Management Development, 1957; Publication (Box 4, Folder 60)
- Box: 4, Folder: 61, Publication (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Item 1: Application for Employment, Publication (Box 4, Folder 61)
- Box: 4, Folder: 62, Publication (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Division, Publication (Box 4, Folder 62)
- Box: 4, Folder: 63, Publication (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Item 1: Careers for Graduating Students and Alumni, 1963; Publication (Box 4, Folder 63)
- Box: 4, Folder: 64, Publication (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Item 1: Office of the Director of Personnel, 1963; Publication (Box 4, Folder 64)
- Box: 4, Folder: 65, Publication (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Training Section, Course Index, 1963; Publication (Box 4, Folder 65)
- Box: 4, Folder: 66, Publication (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Item 1: Credit Union Application for Loan, 1942; Publication (Box 4, Folder 66)
- Box: 4, Folder: 67, Publication (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Item 1: A Request to All Boeing Employees, Publication (Box 4, Folder 67)
- Box: 4, Folder: 68, Publication (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Item 1: Engineering Employment Application, Publication (Box 4, Folder 68)
- Box: 4, Folder: 69, Publication (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Item 1: Apprenticeship Agreement, Publication (Box 4, Folder 69)
- Box: 4, Folder: 70, Publication (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Item 1: Shop Employee Analysis, Publication (Box 4, Folder 70)
- Box: 4, Folder: 71, Publication (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Item 1: Medical Recommendations, 1958; Publication (Box 4, Folder 71)
- Box: 4, Folder: 72, Publication (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Item 1: Manufacturing Training Unit: Training Course Index, 1960; Publication (Box 4, Folder 72)
- Box: 4, Folder: 73, Publication (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Item 1: Aero-Space Division: Recruiting- Record Keeping Data, Publication (Box 4, Folder 73)
- Box: 4, Folder: 74, Publication (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Item 1: The Employee Development Section: Administration Manual, Publication (Box 4, Folder 74)
- Box: 4, Folder: 75, Publication (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Item 1: Functional Work Areas Applicable to College Professional-Technical Disciplines, Publication (Box 4, Folder 75)
- Box: 4, Folder: 76, Publication (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - Item 1: Policy and Procedure Guide Pre-Management Course, Publication (Box 4, Folder 76)
- Box: 4, Folder: 77, Publication (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - Item 1: Industrial Personnel Section, Publication (Box 4, Folder 77)
- Box: 4, Folder: 78, Publication (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - Item 1: Employment, Recruiting and Special Programs Unit Procedures, 1958; Publication (Box 4, Folder 78)
- Box: 4, Folder: 79, Publication (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - Item 1: Developmental Planning: A Guide to the Appraisal and Coaching of Supervisory Personnel, Publication (Box 4, Folder 79)
- Box: 4, Folder: 80, Publication (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - Item 1: Form of Job Description, Publication (Box 4, Folder 80)
- Box: 4, Folder: 81, Publication (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Item 1: Sick Leave, 1949; Publication (Box 4, Folder 81)
- Box: 4, Folder: 82, Publication (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - Item 1: Procedure for Developing Managerial Standards of Performance, 1958; Publication (Box 4, Folder 82)
- Box: 4, Folder: 83, Publication (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - Item 1: Physics at Boeing, 1962; Publication (Box 4, Folder 83)
- Box: 4, Folder: 84, Publication (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Item 1: Structures at Boeing, 1962; Publication (Box 4, Folder 84)
- Box: 4, Folder: 85, Publication (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Item 1: Mechanical Engineering at Boeing, 1962; Publication (Box 4, Folder 85)
- Box: 4, Folder: 86, Publication (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Item 1: Mathematics at Boeing, 1962; Publication (Box 4, Folder 86)
- Box: 4, Folder: 87, Publication (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Item 1: Business Administration at Boeing, 1962; Publication (Box 4, Folder 87)
- Box: 4, Folder: 88, Publication (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - Item 1: Aerodynamics at Boeing, 1962; Publication (Box 4, Folder 88)
- Box: 4, Folder: 89, Publication (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - Item 1: Electronics at Boeing, 1962; Publication (Box 4, Folder 89)
- Box: 4, Folder: 90, Publication (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - Item 1: Information for Production and Maintenance Hourly Employees, Publication (Box 4, Folder 90)
- Box: 4, Folder: 91, Publication (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - Item 1: Employment of Salaried Employees Forms, Publication (Box 4, Folder 91)
- Box: 4, Folder: 92, Publication (Box 4, Folder 92)
  - Item 1: All Manufacturing Division Supervisors, 1949; Publication (Box 4, Folder 92)
- Box: 4, Folder: 93, Publication (Box 4, Folder 93)
  - Item 1: Engineering Development Program, Publication (Box 4, Folder 93)
- Box: 4, Folder: 94, Publication (Box 4, Folder 94)
  - Item 1: Management Appraisal and Coaching Program, 1957; Publication (Box 4, Folder 94)
- Box: 4, Folder: 95, Publication (Box 4, Folder 95)
  - Item 1: Capability Vol.1, Mechanical Laboratories, Publication (Box 4, Folder 95)
- Box: 4, Folder: 96, Publication (Box 4, Folder 96)
  - Item 1: Capability Vol.2, Structures Testing Facilities, Publication (Box 4, Folder 96)
- Box: 4, Folder: 97, Publication (Box 4, Folder 97)
  - Item 1: Capability Vol.3, Materials Technology Laboratory, Publication (Box 4, Folder 97)
- Box: 4, Folder: 98, Publication (Box 4, Folder 98)
  - Item 1: Challenge: Computing and Mathematics, Publication (Box 4, Folder 98)
- Box: 4, Folder: 99, Publication (Box 4, Folder 99)
  - Item 1: Designing with Experimental Stress Analysis, Publication (Box 4, Folder 99)
- Box: 4, Folder: 100, Publication (Box 4, Folder 100)
  - Item 1: Forgings That Fly, Publication (Box 4, Folder 100)
- Box: 4, Folder: 101, Publication (Box 4, Folder 101)
  - Item 1: Assignments in Aerospace Engineering, Publication (Box 4, Folder 101)
- Box: 4, Folder: 102, Publication (Box 4, Folder 102)
  - Item 1: Boeing Helicopters: Engineering Laboratories Research Today for the Aircraft of Tomorrow, Publication (Box 4, Folder 102)
- Box: 4, Folder: 103, Publication (Box 4, Folder 103)
  - Item 1: Design Engineering, Publication (Box 4, Folder 103)
- Box: 4, Folder: 104, Publication (Box 4, Folder 104)
  - Item 1: Got An Idea? Try It, Publication (Box 4, Folder 104)
- Box: 4, Folder: 105, Publication (Box 4, Folder 105)
  - Item 1: Boeing Vertol Division: Vertical Takeoff and Landing Technology, Publication (Box 4, Folder 105)
- Box: 4, Folder: 106, Publication (Box 4, Folder 106)
  - Item 1: Missiles: Yesterday, Today and Tomorrow, Publication (Box 4, Folder 106)
- Box: 4, Folder: 107, Publication (Box 4, Folder 107)
  - Item 1: The First Decade, Publication (Box 4, Folder 107)
- Box: 4, Folder: 108, Publication (Box 4, Folder 108)
  - Item 1: It May Play, But Will It Fly?, Publication (Box 4, Folder 108)
- Box: 4, Folder: 109, Publication (Box 4, Folder 109)
  - Item 1: Three Young Men, Publication (Box 4, Folder 109)
- Box: 4, Folder: 110, Publication (Box 4, Folder 110)
  - Item 1: Our Men in Materials, Publication (Box 4, Folder 110)
- Box: 4, Folder: 111, Publication (Box 4, Folder 111)
  - Item 1: Boeing Magazine, 1961; Publication (Box 4, Folder 111)
- Box: 4, Folder: 112, Publication (Box 4, Folder 112)
  - Item 1: Corporate Policy: Company Support of Employees Participating in College or University Courses, 1965; Publication (Box 4, Folder 112)
- Box: 4, Folder: 113, Publication (Box 4, Folder 113)
  - Item 1: Let's Talk Structures, Publication (Box 4, Folder 113)
- Box: 4, Folder: 114, Publication (Box 4, Folder 114)
  - Item 1: Wired for Ideas, Publication (Box 4, Folder 114)
- Box: 4, Folder: 115, Publication (Box 4, Folder 115)
  - Item 1: Let Your Ideas Fly: Career Sketches in Aerodynamics, Publication (Box 4, Folder 115)
- Box: 4, Folder: 116, Publication (Box 4, Folder 116)
  - Item 1: Boeing Magazine, 1962; Publication (Box 4, Folder 116)
- Box: 4, Folder: 117, Publication (Box 4, Folder 117)
  - Item 1: How You Can Get The Most For One Billion, Nineteen Million, Thirty-Two Thousand, One Hundred Twenty-Eight Dollars and Fourteen Cents, Publication (Box 4, Folder 117)
- Box: 4, Folder: 118, Publication (Box 4, Folder 118)
  - Item 1: Your Guide to Performance Analysis, Publication (Box 4, Folder 118)
- Box: 4, Folder: 119, Publication (Box 4, Folder 119)
  - Item 1: Boeing Bulletins, Publication (Box 4, Folder 119)
- Box: 4, Folder: 120, Publication (Box 4, Folder 120)
  - Item 1: Environment for Dynamic Career Growth, Publication (Box 4, Folder 120)
- Box: 4, Folder: 121, Publication (Box 4, Folder 121)
  - Item 1: Manufacturing Training: Electronics Familiarization, 1958; Publication (Box 4, Folder 121)
- Box: 5, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Retraining in California: 1964 Report, Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Box: 5, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Job Evaluation Plan, Publication (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Box: 5, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Salary Schedules for Administrative Personnel in California Public Junior Colleges, 1968; Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Box: 5, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Personnel Management Series Report No.4: Effective Writing, 1952; Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Box: 5, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Interagency Management Development 1965-1966, Publication (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Box: 5, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: State Secretarial Techniques, 1951; Publication (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Box: 5, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Personnel Management Series Report No.5: Training Films, 1953; Publication (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Box: 5, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Personnel Management Series Report No.2: Job Performance Standards, 1951; Publication (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Box: 5, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Personnel Management Series Report No.3.: Performance Reports, 1951; Publication (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Box: 5, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Personnel Management Series Report No.6: Public Relations is Our Business, 1954; Publication (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Box: 5, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Progress Report 1957-1958 Research and Community Services, Publication (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Box: 5, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Position Classification: A Programmed Text for Supervisors, Publication (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Box: 5, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: University Extension, 1960; Publication (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Box: 5, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: The Executive Program: University of California Berkeley, 1966; Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Box: 5, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Curriculum at University of California Berkeley, 1953; Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Box: 5, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: How Campbell '66' Express Selects and Trains Future Managers, Publication (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Box: 5, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 5, Folder 17)